- Oh. Oh. Shut the door, Shut the door.
- Why?
(Penny:)Just do it.
- Get inside and shut the door.
- Well, you didn't specify.
- Is Leonard around?
- He went to the movies without me.
(Sheldon:)It was the only option.
I'm sorry, I don't know understand
which social situation this is.
(Sheldon:)Could you give me some guidance
how to proceed?
[SIGHS]
(Penny:)The building manager's showing
an apartment downstairs...
(Penny:)- ...and I haven't paid my rent.
- Oh, I see.
I'm not comfortable harboring
a fugitive...
(Sheldon:)...from the 2311
North Los Robles Corporation.
(Penny:)It's no big deal.
I'm just a little behind on my bills.
(Penny:)They cut back my hours
at the restaurant and my car broke down.
(Sheldon:)If you recall...